Guide to the Arnold Sundgaard papers, 1925-1988
George Mason University. Libraries. Special Collections & Archives
- Series 3: Newspaper Clippings, 1935-1976; (boxes 6-8, 43)
  - Spirochete / Everywhere I Roam scrapbook, 1938-1939 (Box 7, Folder 18)
    Includes mostly newspaper clippings, some programs, one photograph.
    - Spirochete
    - Spirochete
  - Theatre, Inc. (newspaper and magazine clippings), 1946 (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - The Underground Reporter (radio series), 1943 (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - This Fallow Ground (newspaper clippings), 1935 (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - Virginia Overture (newspaper clippings), 1946 (Box 8, Folder 4)
- Series 4: Photographs, 1933-1982; (boxes 8, 42, 44)
  Series 4: Photographs (1933-1982) is arranged alphabetically by title and includes photographs of play productions, actors, and Arnold Sundgaard. Photographs of play productions include the plays: Brigham, Down in the Valley, Equinox, Everywhere I Roam, Forests of the Night, Giants in the Earth, The Great Campaign, The First Crocus, Kilgo Run, Knock on Wood, Of Love Remembered, The Promised Valley, Spirochete, This Fallow Ground, and The Truth About Windmills. Images are mostly prints, there are some slides, and some oversize material.
  - George Pierce Baker class photograph (Yale), Spring 1933 (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - Barter Theatre photographs, 1940-1941 (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - Bennington College photographs, 1950 (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - Brigham production photographs, 1976 (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - Down in the Valley at the University of Denver production photographs, 1952 (Box 8, Folder 9)
  - Equinox photographs with cardboard backing (3), 1941 (Oversize 44)
  - Everywhere I Roam at Barter Theatre photographs, 1938 (Box 8, Folder 10)
  - Forests of the Night in Dublin (photographs and set design), 1965 (Box 8, Folder 11)
  - Forests of the Night performed in Akron, Ohio (prints and slides), 1966 (Box 8, Folder 12)
  - Giants in the Earth, grant file and photographs, 1974 (Box 8, Folder 13)
  - The Great Campaign (ANTA experimental theatre), 1947 (Box 8, Folder 14)
  - The Great Campaign, University of Texas, photograph, 1945 (Box 8, Folder 15)
  - Gregory Peck photograph, circa 1955 (Box 8, Folder 16)
  - The Group Theatre (Lakes Grove) photographs, 1939 (Box 8, Folder 17)
  - Jorislund (The First Crocus) at Barter Theatre production photographs, August 1941 (Box 8, Folder 18)
  - Kilgo Run (Los Angeles) production photographs, 1950s (Box 8, Folder 19)
  - Kilgo Run (Arena Theatre, Rochester, NY) production photographs and program, 1952 (Box 8, Folder 20)
  - Knock on Wood photographs, circa 1982 (Box 8, Folder 21)
  - Of Love Remembered (ANTA theatre, NYC) photographs, February 1967 (Box 8, Folder 22)
  - The Promised Valley (Utah) photograph, 1971 (Box 8, Folder 23)
  - Spirochete Chicago photographs, 1938 (Box 8, Folder 24)
  - Spirochete (Philadelphia) photographs, 1939 (Box 8, Folder 25)
    - Spirochete
  - Arnold Sundgaard by Jeremy Sundgaard at Eastman School of Music for "Wind Blows Free", 1973 (Oversize 42)
  - Arnold Sundgaard personal photographs, 1937-1977 (Box 8, Folder 26)
  - Theatre Inc. oversize prints, 1946 (Oversize 42)
    Four 16" x 20" oversize black and white prints with thick board backing. Images depict Theatre, Inc. productions of Playboy of the Western World, Henry IV part I, and Oedipus.
  - Theatre, Inc. Pygmalion (Gertrude Lawrence) photographs, 1946 (Box 8, Folder 27)
  - This Fallow Ground (Yale) production photographs, 1935 (Box 8, Folder 28)
  - The Truth About Windmills (color slides), 1973 (Box 8, Folder 29)
  - The Truth About Windmills (Rochester) production photographs, 1973 (Box 8, Folder 30)
  - University of Illinois playwriting class photographs, 1949 (Box 8, Folder 31)
  - Virginia Overture, Barter Theatre, folk dance scene outside (photograph), 1946 (Box 8, Folder 32)
- Series 5: Playscripts, 1932-1978; (boxes 8-21, 42)
  Series 5: Playscripts (1932-1978) is arranged alphabetically by title and includes primarily playscripts but also radio and television scripts, libretti, outlines, drafts, production notes, scores, programs, costume designs, and some correspondence. Multiple drafts of produced plays are here, as is unfinished scripts and scripts for plays not produced.
  - Akron by Moonlight playscript, July 1959 (Box 8, Folder 33)
  - Akron by Moonlight playscript, circa 1959-1960 (Box 8, Folder 34)
  - Akron by Moonlight playscript, circa 1959-1960 (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - Akron by Moonlight playscript, June-July 1960 (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - Alberta Alone early version playscript, June 1966 (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - Amarillo Strip first draft playscript, 1977-1978 (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - Amarillo Strip final draft playscript, 1978 (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - Ariel de Lancey outline (unfinished play), undated (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - The Ballad of Brigham Young, 1974 (Box 9, Folder 7)
  - The Ballad of Brigham Young (playscript and score), 1975-1976 (Box 9, Folder 8)
  - The Ballad of Brigham Young (production conference memo and playscript), December 9-10, 1974 (Box 9, Folder 9)
  - Brigham, May 1975; April 1976 (Box 10, Folder 1)
    Includes: cassette tape; First you have a dream song lyrics; two "Brigham!" metal pins.
  - Brigham costume design sketches (5), 1970s (Oversize 42)
  - Brigham (musical cue playscript), circa 1974-1976 (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - Material for Brigham, 1975 (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - Notes for Brigham, 1975 (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - Brigham musical for Brigham Young University centennial press conference, 1976 (Box 10, Folder 5)
    Includes: black and white photographs; program; newspaper clipping.
  - Centennial collection, Brigham Young University, 1976 (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - The founders convocation of the 100th anniversary of Brigham Young University 1875-1975 (Box 10, Folder 7)
  - The Beautiful and Anxious Maidens, undated (Box 10, Folder 8)
    Outline for a musical comedy and research material consisting of copies of articles, postcards, and a paper written by Edmund G. Love.
  - The Beautiful and Anxious Maidens, undated (Box 10, Folder 9)
    Outline for a musical comedy by Sundgaard; playscript written by Frances Goodrich and Albert Hackett.
  - Buddy Biloxi (various versions), circa 1950s-1960s (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - The Seven Joys of Buddy Biloxi (playscript, version I), 1955 (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - The Seven Joys of Buddy Biloxi (playscript, version II), 1956 (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - Cumberland Fair playscript, 1953 (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - Derelicts playscript, 1932 (Box 11, Folder 5)
    Sundgaard's first play written in Madison, Wisconsin.
  - Down in the Valley (scripts), 1945; 1974 (Box 11, Folder 6)
    Scripts for a school opera from 1945, and a film version in 1974.
  - The Eagles They Fly High playscript (unfinished play), 1951 (Box 11, Folder 7)
  - The Early Traveler playscript, 1939 (Box 11, Folder 8)
  - Elsie Marley libretto script (unfinished), 1959 (Box 11, Folder 9)
  - Episode at Plumtree Farm playscript (unfinished play), undated (Box 11, Folder 10)
  - Equinox playscript, 1941-1942 (Box 11, Folder 11)
  - Everywhere I Roam playscript, 1937-1938 (Box 12, Folder 1)
  - Everywhere I Roam playscript, 1938 (Box 12, Folder 2)
  - The Flag on Suribachi (radioscript), undated (Box 12, Folder 3)
  - Flossie playscript, circa 1966 (Box 12, Folder 4)
  - Forests of the Night (playscript), circa 1962 (Box 12, Folder 5)
  - Forests of the Night first draft, circa 1960-1962 (Box 12, Folder 6)
  - Forests of the Night original version, 1962 (Box 12, Folder 7)
  - Forests of the Night (playscript taken to MacDowell), April 7, 1963 (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - Forests of the Night (playscript and program), 1962; 1965 (Box 13, Folder 2)
  - Freddie playscript, undated (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - The Gambler playscript, 1940-1942 (Box 13, Folder 4)
  - Giants in the Earth playscript (an opera based on the novel by O.E. Rolvaag), 1949 (Box 13, Folder 5)
  - Giants in the Earth playscript, 1951 (Box 13, Folder 6)
    Performed by the Columbia Opera Workshop March 8 to April 7, 1951.
  - The Glad House playscript, 1941 (Box 13, Folder 7)
    Performed at the University of Virginia, based on characters witnessed at Hotel Delano, Chicago while working for the Federal Theatre.
  - The Great Campaign playscript, 1947 (Box 13, Folder 8)
  - The Great Campaign playscript, 1947 (Box 13, Folder 9)
  - The Great Campaign playscript, circa 1940s (Box 13, Folder 10)
  - The Great Campaign playscript, circa 1940s (Box 14, Folder 1)
  - The Great Campaign playscript, circa 1940s (Box 14, Folder 2)
  - The Greenfield Christmas Tree (libretto, various versions), 1962-1963 (Box 14, Folder 3)
  - Hide and Seek (playscript), circa 1942 (Box 14, Folder 4)
  - Honey in the Horn (outline and script for television play), undated (Box 14, Folder 5)
  - Hotel Cherokee (unpublished novel), circa 1954 (Box 14, Folder 6)
  - Hotel Cherokee (unpublished novel, discard sheets), circa 1950s (Box 14, Folder 7)
  - Hotel Cherokee (unpublished novel, first rough draft), December 1959- January 1960 (Box 14, Folder 8)
  - Hotel Cherokee playscript, 1943 (Box 14, Folder 9)
  - Innocency with Her Open Face playscript; typewritten notes, undated; April 12, 1972 (Box 15, Folder 1)
  - Jorislund (The First Crocus) playscript, circa 1940s (Box 15, Folder 2)
  - Jorislund (The First Crocus) playscript, 1941 (Box 15, Folder 3)
  - Jorislund (The First Crocus) playscript, 1941 (Box 15, Folder 4)
  - Journey to Duluth (radioscript), undated (Box 15, Folder 5)
  - The Kilgo Run playscript, 1952 (Box 15, Folder 6)
  - The Kilgo Run playscript, 1952 (Box 15, Folder 7)
  - The Kilgo Run playscript, circa 1950s (Box 15, Folder 8)
  - The Kilgo Run playscript, circa 1950s (Box 16, Folder 1)
  - Kittiwake Island playscript, 1955 (Box 16, Folder 2)
  - Kittiwake Island playscript, circa 1950s (Box 16, Folder 3)
  - Kittiwake Island (playscript), 1955 (Box 16, Folder 4)
  - The Lady of Lyons (play or television script), undated (Box 16, Folder 5)
  - The Little Prince (playscript), undated (Box 16, Folder 6)
  - The Lowland Sea playscript, 1951 (Box 16, Folder 7)
  - The Lowland Sea playscript, 1952 (Box 16, Folder 8)
  - The Malcontent, 1933 (Box 16, Folder 9)
  - Montparnasse revised playscript, February 3, 1971 (Box 16, Folder 10)
  - Montparnasse working playscript, May 1, 1969 (Box 17, Folder 1)
  - Montparnasse playscript, May 1, 1969 (Box 17, Folder 2)
  - Mosaic playscript, February 3, 1977 (Box 17, Folder 3)
  - Nobody's Earnest playscript, 1973-1978 (Box 17, Folder 4)
  - Nobody's Earnest final working playscript, 1973 (Box 17, Folder 5)
  - Ode to a Railroad ("assorted stabs"), May 1967 (Box 17, Folder 6)
  - Oedipus at Elsinore playscript (unfinished play), undated (Box 17, Folder 7)
  - Of Love Remembered playscript, undated (Box 17, Folder 8)
  - Omnibus [Ford Foundation] for CBS television, undated (Box 17, Folder 9)
    Scripts for Village Incident - India; Jack Be Normal; Four Flags of the Confederacy; Beethoven's Fifth.
  - On Hemlock Brook playscript, 1953 (Box 18, Folder 1)
    Written for Williamstown Bicentennial 1953, directed by David Bryant at Williams College Adams Memorial Theatre.
  - The Opening play playscript, undated (Box 18, Folder 2)
  - The Ordeal of Gordon Fishkill libretto, 1947 (Box 18, Folder 3)
    A comic opera written for post-dinner entertainment at Applegreen Old Westbury, Long Island.
  - Other Kingdom: a musical play (playscript), undated (Box 18, Folder 4)
  - Promised Valley, simplified version, 1958 (Box 18, Folder 5)
    Includes: two playscripts, postcard.
  - Promised Valley (newspaper clippings), 1947-1948 (Box 18, Folder 6)
  - Promised Valley programs and ephemera, 1947 (Box 18, Folder 7)
  - Promised Valley music for Home and Love is my Song, 1947 (Box 18, Folder 8)
  - Promised Valley vocal score and choral parts, 1958 (Box 18, Folder 9)
  - Promised Valley correspondence, 1946-1947 (Box 18, Folder 10)
  - Promised Valley (book and lyrics), 1947; 1958 (Box 18, Folder 11)
  - Promised Valley (working playscript), circa 1947 (Box 18, Folder 12)
  - Promised Valley (1976 playscript), 1976-1977 (Box 18, Folder 13)
  - Quartet for Two Voices playscript, 1932 (Box 19, Folder 1)
    Written for first year class in playwriting at Yale during the Fall of 1932.
  - Report on the Underground (radioscript), 1943 (Box 19, Folder 2)
  - Riley Randall playscript, 1968 (Box 19, Folder 3)
  - School for Clowns outline, 1950 (Box 19, Folder 4)
  - Clown play, undated (Box 19, Folder 5)
  - The Snow Queen playscript (various versions), 1962-1964 (Box 19, Folder 6)
  - The Solution playscript, undated (Box 19, Folder 7)
  - Spirochete notes, 1938 (Box 19, Folder 8)
  - Spirochete playscript, 1938 (Box 19, Folder 9)
  - The Summer Wing playscript, circa 1940s-1950s (Box 20, Folder 1)
  - The Summer Wing playscript (early drafts), 1946-1958 (Box 20, Folder 2)
  - Sunday Excursion playscript, 1953 (Box 20, Folder 3)
  - There are Crimes and Crimes playscript; letter, circa 1945; 1966 (Box 20, Folder 4)
  - This Fallow Ground playscript, 1934 (Box 20, Folder 5)
    Yale workshop 47, first play by Sundgaard to be produced at Yale in 1935, directed by Alexander Dean.
  - A Ticket to Tangiers (television script), undated (Box 20, Folder 6)
  - Tosca Libretto (playscript and notes), 1968 (Box 20, Folder 7)
    Free adaptation in collaboration with Albert Marre for Joan Dehner).
  - Tosca playscript, 1968 (Box 20, Folder 8)
    Adaptation of Sardou play.
  - Tosca translation by Albert Marre, 1968 (Box 20, Folder 9)
  - The Truth About Windmills playscript, October 1973 (Box 21, Folder 1)
  - The Truth About Windmills playscript, circa 1973 (Box 21, Folder 2)
  - Well Met in Kansas playscript, undated (Box 21, Folder 3)
  - A Wilderness Christmas (copies and drafts), 1957 (Box 21, Folder 4)
  - The Wind Blows Free (musical play, script), 1948 (Box 21, Folder 5)
  - The Wind Blows Free (musical play, script), 1948 (Box 21, Folder 6)
  - The Wind Blows Free (revised copy), April 4, 1951 (Box 21, Folder 7)
  - The Wind Blows Free (revised copy), 1951 (Box 21, Folder 8)
  - The Wind Blows Free playscript, circa 1948-1951 (Box 21, Folder 9)
  - Without a Song playscript (first full length play), 1933 (Box 21, Folder 10)
  - Young Abe Lincoln (playscript and drafts), 1961 (Box 21, Folder 11)
- Series 6: Programs and Posters, 1925-1988; (boxes 22-29, oversize folder)
  Series 6: Programs and Posters (1925-1988) is arranged alphabetically by title and includes programs and posters for productions written by Sundgaard as well as programs collected by Sundgaard.
  - Brigham posters (4), 1976 (Oversize folder)
  - Brigham program, April 1976 (Box 22, Folder 1)
  - Brigham programs, 1976 (Box 22, Folder 2)
  - Down in the Valley programs, 1949-1961 (Box 22, Folder 3)
  - Everywhere I Roam programs, 1938 (Box 22, Folder 4)
  - Forests of the Night posters (2), 1965 (Oversize folder)
  - Forests of the Night programs, 1964-1965 (Box 22, Folder 5)
  - Forest of the Night (program), February 16, 1965 (Box 22, Folder 6)
  - Gallantry (program), undated (Box 22, Folder 7)
  - Giants of the Earth programs, 1974 (Box 22, Folder 8)
  - Giants in the Earth program, 1974 (Box 22, Folder 9)
  - The Great Campaign programs, 1945 (Box 22, Folder 10)
  - Jorislund (The First Crocus) programs, 1941-1942 (Box 22, Folder 11)
  - The Kilgo Run programs, 1952 (Box 22, Folder 12)
  - Kittiwake Island program, October 1960 (Box 22, Folder 13)
  - Lowland Sea program, 1950s (Box 22, Folder 14)
  - Miscellaneous, 1941-1961 (Box 22, Folder 15)
  - Miscellaneous, 1983 (Box 22, Folder 16)
  - Mosaic programs, circa 1987 (Box 22, Folder 17)
  - Nobody's Earnest posters, July 1973 (Oversize folder)
    Two posters from the Williamstown Theatre production of Nobdy's Earnest. One has a yellow background with green text and highlights Nobody's Earnest and The Good Woman of Setzuan, the other has a white background, red and blue lettering and features a drawn map at the top.
  - Nobody's Earnest programs, 1973 (Box 22, Folder 18)
  - Of Love Rememberd poster (2), 1967 (Oversize folder)
  - Of Love Remembered at the World Festival "Expo 67" in Montreal, Canada (program), February 1967 (Box 22, Folder 19)
  - Of Love Remembered programs, 1967 (Box 22, Folder 20)
  - Programs - A, 1938-1975 (Box 22, Folder 21)
    America Hurrah; Abssence of a Cello; A Chorus Line; The Actors Studio - Strange Interlude; The Advocate; The Affair; Agatha Sue I Love You; Ain't Misbehavin'; Aldwych Theatre - The Persecution and Assassination of Marat; All American; All the Way Home; Abe Lincoln in Illinois; Absurd Person Singular; ACT (American Conservatory Theatre); After the Rain; The Alchemist; Jack Ruby, All-American Boy; Alvin Ailey: City Center Dance Theater.
  - Programs - A, 1946-1977 (Box 23, Folder 1)
    The American Academy of Arts and Letters and The National Institute of Arts and Letters Ceremonial; American Buffalo; American Repertory Theatre; American Shakespeare Festival Theatre; Anne Meacham; Annie Get Your Gun; APA-Phoenix; APA-Repertory Company; Ashes; The Azuma Kabuki Dancers and Musicians; The American Dream; The American Mime Theatre; Amharclann na Mainistreach; Anastasia; Anniversary Waltz; Applause; Apple of His Eye; The Apple Tree; At the Drop of a Fan; Auntie Mame.
  - Programs - B, 1939-1974 (Box 23, Folder 2)
    The Bad Seed; Baker Street; The Ballad of the Sad Café; Ballet Ballads; The Ballet Russe de Monte Carlo; Barefoot in Athens; The Beggars Opera; Berkshire Festival; Berkshire Music Center; Big Fish, Little Fish; Black Comedy; Boesman and Lena; Claudia; Breakfast in Bedlam; Bad Habits; Bajour; The Beauty Part; Becket; The Bed Before Yesterday; Barefoot in Athens; The Best Man; Billy Budd; The Blacks; The Blood Knot; Borstal Boy; The Boy Friend.
  - Programs - B, 1945-1977 (Box 23, Folder 3)
    Brigadoon; Follow the Girls; Buck Clayton; Bullfight; Bye Bye Birdie; Brigadoon; Brooklyn Academy of Music; The Browning Version; Bus stop; By George; Beggar on Horseback; Bravo.
  - Programs - C, 1945-1977 (Box 23, Folder 4)
    Cabaret; Camelot; Camp Meeting; The Caretaker; Call Me Mister; Camino Real; Can-Can; Carib Song; Carousel; Carnegie Hall; Carry Nation; Cat on a Hot Tin Roof; Catch Me if You Can; The Caucasian Chalk Circle; The Chalk Garden; The Cherry Orchard; The Changing Room; Chapter Two.
  - Programs - C, 1948-1976 (Box 23, Folder 5)
    The Children's Hour; Chips with Everything; Chicago; Chicago Stagebill - High Button Shoes; City Center Joffrey Ballet; The City Center - How to Succeed in Business Without Really Trying; The City Center - Marcel Marceau; Coco; Colored Girls Who Have Considered Suicide with the Rainbow is Enuf; The Chinese and Dr. Fish; The Chinese Prime Minister; A Chorus Line; Circle in the Square; City Center Joffrey Ballet; A Clearing in the Woods; The Climate of Eden; The Cocktail Party; Colette; Come Live With Me; Come Share My House.
  - Programs - C, 1951-1976 (Box 23, Folder 6)
    Comedie Francaise; Company; Compulsion; The Confidential Clerk; Conversations at Midnight; The Creation of the World and Other Business; Cyrano; Comedians; Comedy; Command Performance; Conduct Unbecoming; Courtin' Time; The Crucible; The Country Girl; Cyrano de Bergerac; The Condemned of Altona.
  - Programs - D, 1945-1977 (Box 23, Folder 7)
    The Dark at the Top of the Stairs; Damn Yankees; Dances of Bali; Danny Kaye; Dear Judas; The Deputy; Desire Under the Elms; Dial 'M' For Murder; Diary of a Scoundrel; Dames at Sea; The Dark is Light Enough; Dark of the Moon; The Deadly Game; The Deep Blue Sea; The Desperate Hours; The Diary of Anne Frank; The Deputy; Dickins and Jones; Dirty Linen and New-found-land; Doctor Faustus Lights the Lights; A Doll's House; Do Not Pass Go; The D'Oyly Carte Opera Company of London.
  - Programs - D, 1951-1977 (Box 24, Folder 1)
    The D'Oyly Carte Opera Company of London; Dracula; The Dybbuk; Dutchman; Duel of Angels; Dylan.
  - Programs - E, 1947-1975 (Box 24, Folder 2)
    Eastward in Eden; Edward, My Son; Elizabeth I; The Enemy is Dead; Emergency Broadway Theatre Directory; An Enemy of the People; Enter Laughing; The Entertainer; Entertaining Mr. Sloane; Equus; Erlanger.
  - Programs - F, 1949-1977 (Box 24, Folder 3)
    A Far Country; Fiddler on the Roof; Fair Harvard; Family Business; The Farmers Hotel; Frank Merriwell or Honor Challenged; The Fighting Cock; First One Asleep, Whistle; Faust.
  - Programs - F, 1939-1974 (Box 24, Folder 4)
    Mexicana; Funny Girl; The Four Winds; Follies; Find Your Way Home; Flora and the Red Menace; The Foo Hsing Theatre; A Funny Thing Happened on the Way to the Forum; The Fourposter; Finian's Rainbow; Fiorello!; Flahooley; The Flowering Peach; Fortune and Men's Eyes; Forty Carats.
  - Programs - G, 1925-1977 (Box 24, Folder 5)
    The Gambler; Gentlemen Prefer Blondes; Gideon; The Gin Game; The Glass Menagerie; The Golden Apple; Golden Boy; Georgy; Good Evening; The Great White Hope; Guys and Dolls; Gantry; Garden District; Gemini; Generation; The Gingerbread Lady; Gloria and Esperanza; The Grand Street Follies; Grease; The Green Pastures; Gypsy.
  - Programs - H, 1948-1969 (Box 24, Folder 6)
    Habimah; Hair; Half a Sixpence; Hamlet (at Arena Stage); Harkness Ballet; Hello Dolly!; Hadrian VII; Hail Scrawdyke!; Half in Earnest; Happy Ending and Day of Absence; Harvey; A Hatful of Rain; Helen; Hello Solly!
  - Programs - H, 1939-1971 (Box 24, Folder 7)
    Henry V; High Spirits; Hispania (at SUNY Stony Brook); The Homecoming; Hope's the Thing; The House of Blue Leaves; The House of Bernarda Alba; How to Succeed in Business without Really Trying; Here's Where I Belong; High Button Shoes; The Hollow Crown; Home; The Hostage; Hostile Witness; Hotel Paradiso; Awake and Sing; House of Flowers.
  - Programs - I, 1946-1977 (Box 24, Folder 8)
    I am a Camera; The Immoralist; Impossible on Saturday; The Incomparable Max; Indians; Inherit the Wind; The Innocents; Inquest; The Iceman Cometh; I Love My Wife; Inadmissible Evidence; Inner City; Institute for Advanced Studies in the Theatre Arts (Phedre); In the Summer House; Inside U.S.A.; In the Bar of a Tokyo Hotel.
  - Programs - I, 1957-1969 (Box 25, Folder 1)
    I was Dancing; The Irish Players; Iphigenia in Aulis; Invitation to a March; Ivanov; The Investigation; In the Matter of J. Robert Oppenheimer.
  - Programs - J, 1947-1973 (Box 25, Folder 2)
    Jamaica; Joe Egg; John Loves Mary; Jose Greco and his Company; Jacques Brel is alive and well and living in Paris; Jimmy; The Jockey Club Stakes; The John Drew Theater; John Murray Anderson's Almanac.
  - Programs - K, 1950-1975 (Box 25, Folder 3)
    The King and I; Kiss Me Kate; King Lear; The Knack; Knickerbocker Holiday; The Killing of Sister George; King of Hearts; Kennedy's Children; The Lady's Not for Burning; The King and I.
  - Programs - L, 1939-1976 (Box 25, Folder 4)
    The Lady of the Camellias; The Lady from the Sea; Landscape of the Body; La Grosse Valise; La Plume de ma Tante; The Last Analysis; The Latent Heterosexual; Leave it to Jane; Lenny; Leonard Sillman's New Faces of 1952; Leonard Sillman's New Faces of 1968; The Little Foxes; Little Murders; The Lark; The Last of Mrs. Lincoln; Last of the Red Hot Lovers; Leave it to Jane; The Lion in Winter.
  - Programs - L, 1938-1977 (Box 25, Folder 5)
    A Little Night Music; London Assurance; On Borrowed Time; Look Homeward, Angel; Lovers and Other Strangers; Lute Song; Luther; Lincoln Center: American Ballet Theatre; Look Back in Anger; Loot; The Love of Four Colonels; Lord Pengo; The Little Foxes.
  - Programs - M, 1939-1974 (Box 25, Folder 6)